Guide to the Pennsylvania Economy League Records, 1925-1985 AIS.1978.06
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- Counties, 1937-1987; III.
  - Fayette, "Fayette County Assessed Value of Taxable Real Estate 1959-1960", July, 1960
  - Fayette, "Fayette County Assessed Value of Taxable Real Estate 1960-1961", July, 1961
  - Fayette, "Fayette County Assessed Value of Taxable Real Estate 1961-1962", July, 1962
  - Fayette, "Fayette County Assessed Value of Taxable Real Estate 1963-1964", April, 1964
  - Fayette, "Fayette County and Fayette County Institution District 1944 Budget", March, 1944
  - Fayette, "Fayette County and Fayette County Institution District Statement of Income and Expenditures to March 31, 1945", May, 1945
  - Fayette, "Fayette County Final Census Report 1960", July, 1961
  - Fayette, "Fayette County Finances and 1961 Budget Review", August, 1961
  - Fayette, "Fayette County at Midyear a Six Month Review of the General Fund", August, 1963
  - Fayette, "Fayette County Municipal Assessed Valuations and Tax Rates for 1945", May, 1965
  - Fayette, "Fayette County Nine Month Financial Analysis", November, 1961
  - Fayette, "Fayette County Position Classification Project", August, 1979
  - Fayette, "An Interim Report Concerning 1. Admission Policies and Procedures, 2. Patients Fun. 3. County Farm Operation", July, 1968
  - Fayette, "A New County Home for Fayette County", February, 1966
  - Fayette, "A Plan for Improving the Assessment Procedures for Fayette County", November, 1951
  - Fayette, "A Plan for the Revaluation of Property for Tax Purposes in Fayette County", December, 1950
  - Fayette, "A Planning Program for Fayette County", September, 1955
  - Fayette, "A Position Classification and Pay Plan for Fayette County", April, 1970
  - Fayette, "Recommendations for Increasing Efficiency in the Administrations of Estates", December, 1964
  - Fayette, "Report on the 1945 Budget of Fayette County and Fayette County Institutional District", April, 1945
  - Fayette, "Report on the 1946 Budget of Fayette County and Fayette County Institutional District", November, 1946
  - Fayette, "A Six Month Review of the County's Financial Operation", September, 1960
  - Fayette, "A Study of the Administrative Procedures of the Domestic Relations and Probation Offices of the Fayette County Court of Common Pleas", June, 1977
  - Greene, "The Care of Adult Dependents in Curry Memorial Home and Greene Hills Farm of the Institution District of Greene", March, 1960
  - Greene, "Care of the Aged and Infirm in Greene County", November, 1974
  - Greene, "A Comparative Analysis of the Fifth to Eighth Class County Retirement Law and the Municipal Employees' Retirement System", October, 1961
  - Greene, "Comparison of Tax Rates and Property Valuations in Greene County", November, 1964
  - Greene, "Curry Memorial Home: Public or Private", October, 1976
  - Greene, "A Fiscal Review of Greene County Townships for 1964", October, 1965
  - Greene, "Greene County Assessed Valuation of Taxable Real Estate and Tax Rates 1949 and 1948", September, 1949 (Box 33)
  - Greene, "Greene County Assessed Valuation of Taxable Real Estate and Tax Rates 1950, 1949, and 1948", September, 1950
  - Greene, "Greene County Assessed Valuation of Taxable Real Estate and Tax Rates 1954 (Including Tax Collectors as of Election of November, 1953)", August, 1954
  - Greene, "Greene County Assessed Valuation of Taxable Real Estate and Tax Rates 1955", August, 1955
  - Greene, "Greene County Assessed Valuation of Taxable Real Estate and Tax Rates 1951 and 1952", September, 1951
  - Greene, "Greene County Computer Feasibility Study", July, 1981
  - Greene, "Greene County Fiscal Picture: A Review of the 1965 Greene County Budget", April, 1965
  - Greene, "Greene County Fiscal Study: History and Projections 1973-1981", November, 1978
  - Greene, "A Look at the Greene County Budget for the Year 1964", April, 1964
  - Greene, "Greene County Valuations and Tax Rates 1956 and 1957", August, 1957
  - Greene, "Greene County Valuations and Tax Rates 1960", August, 1960
  - Greene, "Greene County Valuations and Tax Rates 1961", July, 1961
  - Greene, "Greene County Valuations and Tax Rates 1962", June, 1962
  - Greene, "Greene County Valuations and Tax Rates 1963", June, 1963
  - Greene, "Greene County Valuations and Tax Rates 1965", July, 1965
  - Greene, "The Impact of a 35 Percent Ratio on County Finances", October, 1960
  - Greene, "Memorandum Report on Greene County Financial Operations Jan. 1, 1958 – Oct. 1, 1958", November, 1958
  - Greene, "Memorandum Report on Job Description and Qualifications for Greene County Director of Adult Welfare Services", February, 1962
  - Greene, "Memorandum Report on Tables of Organization and Salary Schedules for the Employees of the Greene County Homes and Hospitals", February, 1963
  - Greene, "The New Real Estate Appraisal in Greene County and the Effect on the Political Subdivisions of a 25-30-35% Ratio for Taxing Purposes", May, 1955
  - Greene, "A Nine Month Review of Greene County's 1949 Budget and the Projected Year-End Financial Status", November, 1949
  - Greene, "Organizing for Development; A Discussion of the Objectives and Methods of County Planning and Development", May, 1956
  - Greene, "Planned Development for Greene County", January, 1959
  - Greene, "A Plan for a Modern County Program", February, 1961
  - Greene, "Position Classification and Pay Plan for Greene County", November, 1970
  - Greene, "Recent Economic Trends in Greene County", January, 1963
  - Greene, "A Report on the Financial Operations of Greene County 1945-1948 and the 1949 Budget", April, 1949
  - Greene, "A Study of Child Welfare Operation and Services in Greene County, Pennsylvania", June, 1964
  - Greene, "A Study to Determine the Capacity and Facilities Needed at Curry Memorial Home", March, 1962
  - Greene, "A Study of the Office of the board of Assessment and Revision of Taxes", June, 1956
  - Greene, "A Ten-Month Review of Greene County's 1950 Budget and the Projected year-End Financial Status", December, 1950
  - Greene, "Townships Deserve Your Attention", November, 1952
  - Greene, "Union Merger Jointure", February, 1961
  - Lancaster, "Data Relating to the Property valuations and Taxes of Lancaster County and its Municipal Subdivisions", December, 1959
  - Lancaster, "Data Relating to the Property valuations and Taxes of Lancaster County and its Municipal Subdivisions", October, 1960
  - Lancaster, "Indebtedness in Lancaster County", March, 1959
  - Lancaster, "The Pennsylvania Economy League", November, 1958
  - Lancaster, "Job Classification and Pay Plan", December, 1964
  - Lawrence, "County of Lawrence Position Classification and Compensation System", October, 1973
  - Lawrence, "Greater New Castle Association, Greater Newcastle Development Corporation, Lawrence County Industrial Development Authority: A Study of Organizational Relationships", July, 1980
  - Lawrence, "Lawrence County Wage and Salary Study", June, 1977
  - Lehigh, "Cedarbrook: A Survey of Management and Services", April, 1958
  - Lehigh, "Lehigh County Finances 1942 to 1946 Inclusive and the 1947 Budget," March, 1947
  - Lehigh, "Report to Board of County Commissioners of Lehigh County on an Administrative Survey of the Institution District", July, 1943
  - Luzerne, "Administrative Survey of the Luzerne County Planning Commission", February, 1963
  - Luzerne, "Children Come First", November, 1962
  - Luzerne, "Luzerne County Finances", January, 1956
  - Luzerne, "The Luzerne County Planning Commission", January, 1958
  - Luzerne, "Luzerne County Personnel: A Study of Employee Utilization Position Classification Rates of Pay", January, 1957
  - Luzerne, "Luzerne County Tax Rates 1953 -1957", November, 1957
  - Luzerne, "A New System of Real Estate Assessment", February, 1957
  - Luzerne, "Progress Report Relative to Personnel Utilization", November, 1957
  - Luzerne, "A Report on Area Planning for Education in Central Luzerne County", January, 1959
  - Luzerne, "A Study of the Organization for Administration of Education in Lower Luzerne County", July, 1953
  - Lycoming, "Job Classification and Pay Plan", February, 1962
  - Lycoming, "Lycoming County Classification and Pay Plan", August, 1954
  - Philadelphia, "Report of Survey of the Records and Filing Equipment in the Orphans Court", March, 1949
  - McKean, "Report to County Commission of McKean County on Administration of the Institution District", December, 1938 (Box 34)
  - Mercer, "CATV Franchise Information", 1971
  - Mercer, "A Comprehensive Salary Schedule for Mercer County Employees", January, 1962
  - Mercer, "County of Mercer: An Analysis of the Financial Operations for the Years 1940-1945: With a Summation of the 1946 Budget", February, 1946
  - Mercer, "Memorandum Report on Financing Sewer Plant Improvement", December, 1959
  - Mercer, "Mercer County Administrative Study", September, 1977
  - Mercer, "Mercer County Administrative Study", January, 1978
  - Mercer, "Mercer County Administrative Study", August, 1978
  - Mercer, "Mercer County: The Financial Story of 1946 and 1947", May, 1947
  - Mercer, "Mercer County Labor Market Survey", November, 1980
  - Mercer, "Mercer County Institution District: $1,700,000 Proposed Bond Issue", March, 1959
  - Mercer, "Mercer County Skill Needs Survey", July, 1978
  - Mercer, "Personnel Rules and Regulations County of Mercer", May, 1971
  - Mercer, "A Proposed Position Classification Pay Plan for Mercer County", May, 1971
  - Mercer, "A Proposed Position Classification Pay Plan for the Mercer County Housing Authority", August, 1970
  - Mercer, "A Proposed Position Classification Plan for Mercer County", November, 1961
  - Mercer, "Proposed 1978 Salary Ranges, Mercer County Row Office Deputies & Supervisory Personnel", December, 1977
  - Mercer, "Report of Committee to Study and Report on Practices, Procedures and Policies for Selected Department within Mercer County Government", October, 1976
  - Mercer, "A Survey of the Accounting System for the County of Mercer", December, 1958
  - Mercer, "A Study to Determine the Advisability of Establishing a Valley-Wide System of Refuse Collection and/or Disposal", May, 1957
  - Mercer, "A Study to Determine the Capacity and Type of Building Requirements Needed by the Mercer County Institution District Home and Hospital", January, 1958
  - Montgomery, "Analysis of a Proposed Refuse Disposal Project of Lower Merion Township, Montgomery County, Pennsylvania", March, 1960
  - Montgomery, "Comparative County Finance Montgomery County", July, 1956
  - Montgomery, "The Cost of Government in the 24 Borough of Montgomery County", June, 1946
  - Montgomery, "The Cost of Government in the Nine First-Class Townships of Montgomery County", July, 1947
  - Montgomery, "Montgomery County Financial Analysis", June, 1959
  - Montgomery, "Refuse Collection and Disposal", 1962
  - Montgomery, "Twenty-five years of County Operations a Fiscal Study", December, 1944
  - Northampton, "Gracedale: An Administrative and Fiscal Survey", December, 1956
  - Schuylkill, "Somethin's Gotta Give!", November, 1962
  - Sullivan, "The Proposed Construction of a New Secondary School Center in Sullivan County", June, 1962
  - Washington, "An Analysis of Washington County's Budget for 1969", May, 1969
  - Washington, "The Average Family Tax Burden of Washington County Municipalities and Related Trends", April, 1970
  - Washington, "Multiperil Insurance Specifications: City of Monongahela Washington County, Pennsylvania", April, 1972
  - Washington, "Physical and Financial Planning – Capital Budget for Washington County", February, 1969
  - Washington, "Recommended Accounting Improvements for the Controller's Office Washington County, Pennsylvania," February, 1975
  - Washington, "Report of the Administration of the Institution District of Washington County", February, 1939
  - Washington, "Report on the 1944 Budget of Washington County"
  - Washington, "Report on the 1945 Budget Estimates of Washington County", March, 1945
  - Washington, "A Report on the Financial Ramification of Operating the County Farm", March, 1962
  - Washington, "A Report on Washington County's 1956 Financial Operations and the 1957 Budget", April, 1957
  - Washington, "A Report on the Space Utilization and Requirement of Nine County Agencies", October, 1961
  - Washington, "A Review of the Washington County Institution District and Juvenile Detention Home", November, 1943
  - Washington, "A Survey of the Administrative Organization and Management of Washington County Report I: The County Farm – An Asset or a Liability?", December, 1958
  - Washington, "A Study of the Washington County Homes for the Aged", June, 1964
  - Washington, "A Survey Report on the Washington County Institution District", April, 1953
  - Washington, "Washington County Assessed Valuations, Tax Rates and market Values 1958", October, 1958 (Box 35)
  - Washington, "Washington County Assessed Valuations, Tax Rates and market Values 1959", September, 1959
  - Washington, "Washington County Assessed Valuations, Tax Rates and market Values 1961", November, 1961
  - Washington, "Washington County Assessed Valuations, Tax Rates and market Values 1962", September, 1962
  - Washington, "Washington County Assessed Valuations, Tax Rates and market Values 1963", August, 1963
  - Washington, "Washington County Employment Data General Fund", January, 1956
  - Washington, "Washington County Employment Data Institution District", January, 1956
  - Washington, "The Washington County Government Building", May, 1978
  - Washington, "In Preparation for a Countywide Reassessment", June, 1977
  - Westmoreland, "1944 Fall Budget Analysis for Westmoreland County", October, 1944
  - Westmoreland, "1945 Fall Budget Analysis for Westmoreland County", December, 1945
  - Westmoreland, "1962 Municipal Tax Rates 1962-63 School District Tax Rates Westmoreland County", July, 1962
  - Westmoreland, "An Appraisal of Child Welfare Services in Westmoreland County", October, 1945
  - Westmoreland, "Assessment Procedure in Westmoreland County", March, 1943
  - Westmoreland, "Automobile Liability and Physical Damage Specifications: City of Jeannette Westmoreland County, Pennsylvania", March, 1971
  - Westmoreland, "The County Government and the Free Care Problem of the Voluntary Hospitals in Westmoreland County", October, 1963
  - Westmoreland, "The County Planning Program an Appraisal", November, 1961
  - Westmoreland, "Development of an Effective Program for the County Recreation Commission", March, 1958
  - Westmoreland, "Factors Influencing the Financial Operation of the Children's Home of Westmoreland County", September, 1962
  - Westmoreland, "Fall Budget Analysis for Westmoreland County", October, 1943
  - Westmoreland, "Financing Community Recreation", September, 1964
  - Westmoreland, "Improving the Collection of Delinquent Real Estate Taxes in Westmoreland County", November, 1973
  - Westmoreland, "The League Reviews the Tax Base: An Analysis of Assessment Trends in Westmoreland County", September, 1950
  - Westmoreland, "Notes on Recreation", May, 1957
  - Westmoreland, "Organizing for Planning: A Discussion of the Objectives and Methods of County Planning", April, 1956
  - Westmoreland, "Report on the Bonded Debt and Sinking Fund of Westmoreland County", December, 1942
  - Westmoreland, "Report on the 1943 Budget of Westmorland County", February, 1943
  - Westmoreland, "Report on the 1944 Budget of Westmoreland County", February, 1944
  - Westmoreland, "Report on the 1945 Budget of Westmoreland County", March, 1945
  - Westmoreland, "Report on the 1946 Budget of Westmoreland County", March, 1946
  - Westmoreland, "Report to County Commissioners of Westmoreland County on Administration of the Institution District", January, 1938
  - Westmoreland, "A Report on the Operations of the Westmoreland County Home and Farms", April, 1953
  - Westmoreland, "Some Pertinent Problems Relating to the Westmoreland County Jail", March, 1954
  - Westmoreland, "A Study of County Jail Needs in Westmoreland County", September, 1962
  - Westmoreland, "A Study of Court House and Jail Facilities with Recommendations for Improvements", April, 1957
  - Westmoreland, "A Study of the Needs for a Program of the Modern Care for Adult Dependents in the Westmoreland County Home and Infirmary", September, 1965
  - Westmoreland, "Supplement to Factors Influencing the Financial Operation of the Children's Home of Westmoreland County", October, 1962
  - Westmoreland, "Survey of the Office of Recorder of Deeds County of Westmoreland", September, 1953
  - Westmoreland, "A Survey Report on the Need, Scope and Operation of an Area Technical School for Central-Western Westmoreland County", June, 1960
  - Westmoreland, "Ten-Month Review of the 1946 Budget Westmoreland County", December, 1946
  - Westmoreland, "Ten Months Review of Westmoreland County's 1947 Budget", December, 1947
  - Westmoreland, "Volkswagen Impact Study Part II: Impact Statement", March, 1978
  - Westmoreland, "Westmoreland County Airport Authority Phase 1: Current Financial Position and Outlook for 1978", December, 1977
  - Westmoreland, "The Westmoreland county Budget in 1946 and 1947", February, 1947
  - Westmoreland, "The Westmoreland County Budget 1948 Fall Analysis Indicates a Deficit", December, 1948
  - Westmoreland, "The Westmoreland County Budget The Upswing and in Demands and Costs Catches up in 1949", March, 1949
  - Westmoreland, "Westmoreland County Finances 1947 Experience and 1948 Budget", March, 1948
  - Westmoreland, "Westmoreland County Position Classification Selected job Descriptions Personnel Rules and Regulations Salary Sales", October, 1969
  - Wise, "Final Report of the Purchasing/Inventory Control Task Force, Wise County Program", January, 1983
  - York, "Pleasant Acres an Administrative Survey of the York County Institution District Home", July, 1956
- State (PA) Wide Reports, 1936-1982; IV.
  The State (PA) Wide Reports series consists of studies and reports that focus on state government or on state wide issues that affect multiple county and municipal governments. The reports primarily focus on budgets, appropriations, taxation, and utilities.
  - "An Administrative Management Division", July 1954 (Box 36)
  - "Appalachia PA – Background Report", 1966
  - "The Area Redevelopment Act: Summary of Activities of the SE PA Area Redevelopment Council", August 1961
  - "An Area Trade and Industry Survey and a Recommended Vocational Education Program: The Problems of Small High Schools", 1950
  - "Assessment Schedules in Counties: Their Role in Implementing the Uniform Fiscal Calendar", October 16, 1962
  - "Audit of Implementation of Recommendations of the Governor's Review of Government Management, Inc.: Final Report", June 30, 1975
  - "Audit of Implementation of Recommendations of the Governor's Review of Government Management, Inc: Reports 1-6", August 1960 - September 1960
  - "Authorities – Pro and Con: Experience with Authorities in PA", 1954
  - "Behind the Scenes of Municipal Accounting", April 1945
  - "Comparative-Salary Study of the Employees of PA's Sixteenth Sixth-Class Counties", April, 1958
  - "Comparison of Pension Provisions for Municipal Employees in 10 Cities of over 750,000 Population", September 26, 1956
  - "A Comparison of Salaries and Wages for selected Counties and Institution Districts", 1955
  - "A Compilation of Tax Materials for the Department of Commerce Commonwealth of PA", July, 1956
  - "Connellsville State General Hospital: Options for the Future", September, 1981
  - "Constitutional Debt Limits for Local Governments in PA", October, 1958
  - "Desirable Changes in the System of Local Government in PA", October, 1936
  - "Directory", July 1954
  - "A Draft of the Proposed Real Estate Tax sale for PA", January, 1947
  - "Final Long Range Report of the Governor's Tax Study and Revision Commission", December, 1968
  - "Final Long Range Report of The Governor's Tax Study Revision Commission: Abstract", December, 1968
  - "Final Report of the Classification and Compensation Survey of the Administrative Office of PA Courts and the PA Supreme Court, PA Superior Court, and PA Commonwealth Court", September, 1978
  - "Final Report of the Classification and Compensation Survey of the Administrative Office of PA Courts and the PA Supreme Court, PA Superior Court, and PA Commonwealth Court: Trends in Educational Effort", August, 1960
  - "Final Report of the Classification and Compensation Survey of the Administrative Office of PA Courts and the PA Supreme Court, PA Superior Court, and PA Commonwealth Court: Where the Education Dollar Goes", August, 1960
  - "Final Report of the Classification and Compensation Survey of the Administrative Office of PA Courts and the PA Supreme Court, PA Superior Court, and PA Commonwealth Court: The Local Education Effort", September, 1960
  - "Final Report of the Classification and Compensation Survey of the Administrative Office of PA Courts and the PA Supreme Court, PA Superior Court, and PA Commonwealth Court: State Education Effort", September, 1960
  - "Financing PA's Public Works Needs", September 26, 1958
  - "Financing Patient Care: Volume I", 1961
  - "Financing Patient Care: Volume II", 1961
  - "A Fiscal Calendar for PA Local Governments", April 26, 1962
  - "Fiscal Implications of the PA Constitution", September 10, 1958
  - "Fringe Benefits for Public Employees in 47 Selected Communities", 1969
  - "Functional Survey of The Department of Banking and The PA Securities Commission", December 10, 1952
  - "General Fund Budget Estimates", February 12, 1959
  - "Higher Education and the Economy: A Survey of the Impacts on PA's Economy of its Colleges and Universities: The Statewide Impacts", November, 1981
  - "Hospital Cost Study", March, 1965
  - "Improving the State Public Assistance Program", November, 1952
  - "Intake to Public Assistance in PA", July, 1972
  - "Joint State Government Commission on Preliminary Tax Date", 1936
  - "Legal Provisions for State Subsidies in PA", May 8, 1944
  - "Local Government Retirement in PA", October, 1967 (Box 37)
  - "Major Governmental Functions and Allocation by Law to the Various Governmental Units", April 6, 1944
  - "The Middle Road: an evaluation of blue cross service by the PEL", Date not given
  - "Municipal Retirement Legislation in PA", February 14, 1955
  - "Organization and Management of the PA Historical and Museum Commission", October, 1954
  - "PA Legislator's Time Requirements", June, 1978
  - "PA's Capital Budget Procedures: A Review & Evaluation of the Procedures for Planning & Executing the Commonwealth's Capital Budget", May, 1962
  - "Pattern and Projections for Financing Capital Improvements", October, 1960
  - "Penjerdel Adaptability Study Part I: Local Government in a Regional Setting: Adaption to Change", 1964
  - "Penjerdel Adaptability Study Part III: Adaptability of Local Government in Six Municipalities in New Jersey Portion of Penjerdel Region", 1964
  - "Penjerdel Adaptability Study Part IV: Adaptability of Local Governments in Newark, Delaware – Newark Special School District – Ashbourne Hills - Brookside", 1964
  - "Penjerdel Governmental Studies: Monogram No. 1: Historical Development of Local Government in the Penjderdel Region", December 1961
  - "Penjerdel Governmental Studies: Monograph No. 2: Geographical Development and Population Growth in the Penjerdel Regions", March 1962
  - "Penjerdel Governmental Studies: Monograph No. 3: Present Organization of Local Government in the Penjerdel Region", June 1962
  - "Penjerdel Governmental Studies: Monograph No. 4: Distribution of Functions Among Local Government Units in the Penjerdel Regions", August, 1962
  - "The Pennsylvania Department of Highways", November, 1952
  - "Planning for PA's Public Works Needs", April 24, 1958